Boston Streets Collection MS102
Tufts Archival Research Center
- Boston City Directories, 1845 -- 1925; 1845 -- 1960; MS102.002; 2703 Digital Object(s)
  - 1885, MS102.002.009; 227 Digital Object(s)
    - Geo. T. McLauthlin & Co. - The Magic Crusher, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00034; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
      Page image of Geo. T. McLauthlin & Co. - The Magic Crusher from the 1885 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Dickinson Type Foundery, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00035; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
      Page image of Dickinson Type Foundery from the 1885 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00036; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00037; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Lynn and Boston Railroad Co. - Highland Street Railroad Co., 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00038; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
      Page image of Lynn and Boston Railroad Co. - Highland Street Railroad Co. from the 1885 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00039; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Smith & Anthony Stove Co., 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00040; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
      Page image of Smith & Anthony Stove Co. from the 1885 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - J.J. Arakelyan, Printer, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00041; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
      Page image of J.J. Arakelyan, Printer from the 1885 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00042; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00043; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00044; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00045; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00046; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00047; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00048; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00049; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - N.Y. Exhaust Ventilator Co. - Boston Chain Works, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00050; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
      Page image of N.Y. Exhaust Ventilator Co. - Boston Chain Works from the 1885 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00051; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00052; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00053; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Revere Rubber Co., 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00054; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
      Page image of Revere Rubber Co. from the 1885 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Holmes & Blanchard, Mill Furnishers, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00055; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
      Page image of Holmes & Blanchard, Mill Furnishers from the 1885 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Austin C. Wellington Coal Company, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00056; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
      Page image of Austin C. Wellington Coal Company from the 1885 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Henry A. Turner & Co. - Peter Gray, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00057; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
      Page image of Henry A. Turner & Co. - Peter Gray from the 1885 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Rogers & Co. Importers - C.H. McKenney & Co., 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00058; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
      Page image of Rogers & Co. Importers - C.H. McKenney & Co. from the 1885 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00059; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00060; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00061; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00062; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00063; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00064; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00065; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00066; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00067; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00068; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00069; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00070; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00071; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00072; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Wm. T. Foster & Co. - Hawthorne & Co., Plumbers, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00073; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
      Page image of Wm. T. Foster & Co. - Hawthorne & Co., Plumbers from the 1885 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - The Atlantic Works - S.E. Chubbuck & Sons, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00074; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
      Page image of The Atlantic Works - S.E. Chubbuck & Sons from the 1885 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00075; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00076; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00077; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00078; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00079; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00080; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00081; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00082; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00083; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00084; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00085; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00086; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00087; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00088; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00089; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00090; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00091; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Rockwell & Churchill, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00092; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
      Page image of Rockwell & Churchill from the 1885 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Rockwell & Churchill, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00093; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00094; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00095; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00096; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00097; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00098; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00099; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00100; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00101; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00102; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00103; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00104; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00105; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00106; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00107; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00108; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00109; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Newton Morton & Co. - W.O. Taylor & Co., 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00110; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
      Page image of Newton Morton & Co. - W.O. Taylor & Co. from the 1885 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - L.M. Ham & Co. - Central Iron Foundry, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00111; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
      Page image of L.M. Ham & Co. - Central Iron Foundry from the 1885 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00112; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00113; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00114; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00115; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00116; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00117; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00118; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00119; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - The Plume & Atwood Manufacturing Co., 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00120; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
      Page image of The Plume & Atwood Manufacturing Co. from the 1885 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Maverick National Bank, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00121; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
      Page image of Maverick National Bank from the 1885 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Paine's Furniture Company, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00122; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
      Page image of Paine's Furniture Company from the 1885 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Rice, Kendall, & Co., 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00123; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
      Page image of Rice, Kendall, & Co. from the 1885 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Jones, McDuffee, & Stratton, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00124; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
      Page image of Jones, McDuffee, & Stratton from the 1885 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Dennison Mfg. Co., 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00125; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
      Page image of Dennison Mfg. Co. from the 1885 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - John Briggs & Co. - Boston Lead Manufacturing Co., 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00126; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
      Page image of John Briggs & Co. - Boston Lead Manufacturing Co. from the 1885 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - The Standard Life-Saving Mattress Co. - Alfred Hale & Co., 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00127; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
      Page image of The Standard Life-Saving Mattress Co. - Alfred Hale & Co. from the 1885 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00128; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00129; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00130; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00131; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00132; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00133; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00134; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00135; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00136; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00137; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00138; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00139; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00140; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00141; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Theodore Metcalf & Co. Pharmaceutical Chemists, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00142; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
      Page image of Theodore Metcalf & Co. Pharmaceutical Chemists from the 1885 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Codman & Shurtleff, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00143; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
      Page image of Codman & Shurtleff from the 1885 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00144; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00145; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00146; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00147; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00148; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00149; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00150; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00151; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00152; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00153; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00154; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00155; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00156; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00157; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00158; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00159; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00160; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00161; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00162; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00163; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00164; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00165; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00166; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00167; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00168; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00169; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00170; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00171; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00172; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00173; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - John P. Squire & Co., 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00174; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
      Page image of John P. Squire & Co. from the 1885 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Lowell Machine Shop, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00175; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
      Page image of Lowell Machine Shop from the 1885 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00176; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00177; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00178; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00179; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00180; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00181; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00182; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00183; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00184; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00185; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00186; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00187; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00188; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00189; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - R.F. Hawkins' Iron Works - B.F. Sturtevant, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00190; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
      Page image of R.F. Hawkins' Iron Works - B.F. Sturtevant from the 1885 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Boston Bridge Works - Charles H. North & Co., 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00191; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
      Page image of Boston Bridge Works - Charles H. North & Co. from the 1885 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00192; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00193; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00194; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00195; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00196; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00197; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00198; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00199; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00200; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00201; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00202; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00203; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00204; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00205; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Redding, Baird, & Co., 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00206; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
      Page image of Redding, Baird, & Co. from the 1885 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Abram French & Co., 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00207; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
      Page image of Abram French & Co. from the 1885 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00208; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00209; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Reversible Collar Co. - American Fire Hose Mfg. Co., 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00210; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
      Page image of Reversible Collar Co. - American Fire Hose Mfg. Co. from the 1885 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00211; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00212; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00213; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00214; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00215; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00216; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00217; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00218; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00219; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Matthews, Northrup, & Co. - Charles M. Clapp & Co., 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00220; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
      Page image of Matthews, Northrup, & Co. - Charles M. Clapp & Co. from the 1885 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - The Boston Evening Transcript, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00221; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
      Page image of The Boston Evening Transcript from the 1885 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Bancroft & Dyer - Nathan Neat & Co., 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00222; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
      Page image of Bancroft & Dyer - Nathan Neat & Co. from the 1885 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - George H. Mason & Co. - Nathaniel Tufts, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00223; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
      Page image of George H. Mason & Co. - Nathaniel Tufts from the 1885 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00224; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00225; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00226; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
    - Advertisements, 1885; MS102.002.009.DO.00227; Sampson, Murdock, & Co.
  - 1905, MS102.002.010; 395 Digital Object(s)
    This sub-series contains the Boston directory for 1905.
    - Advertisements., 1905; MS102.002.010.DO.00001; Sampson & Murdock Co.
      Page image of Advertisements from the 1905 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements., 1905; MS102.002.010.DO.00002; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements., 1905; MS102.002.010.DO.00003; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - New map of central portion of Boston., 1905; MS102.002.010.DO.00004; Sampson & Murdock Co.
      Page image of New map of central portion of Boston from the 1905 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Advertisements., 1905; MS102.002.010.DO.00005; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements., 1905; MS102.002.010.DO.00006; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements., 1905; MS102.002.010.DO.00007; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements., 1905; MS102.002.010.DO.00008; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements., 1905; MS102.002.010.DO.00009; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements., 1905; MS102.002.010.DO.00010; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements., 1905; MS102.002.010.DO.00011; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements., 1905; MS102.002.010.DO.00012; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements., 1905; MS102.002.010.DO.00013; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements., 1905; MS102.002.010.DO.00014; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements., 1905; MS102.002.010.DO.00015; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements., 1905; MS102.002.010.DO.00016; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements., 1905; MS102.002.010.DO.00017; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements., 1905; MS102.002.010.DO.00018; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements., 1905; MS102.002.010.DO.00019; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements., 1905; MS102.002.010.DO.00020; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements., 1905; MS102.002.010.DO.00021; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements., 1905; MS102.002.010.DO.00022; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements., 1905; MS102.002.010.DO.00023; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements., 1905; MS102.002.010.DO.00024; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements., 1905; MS102.002.010.DO.00025; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements., 1905; MS102.002.010.DO.00026; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements., 1905; MS102.002.010.DO.00027; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements., 1905; MS102.002.010.DO.00028; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements., 1905; MS102.002.010.DO.00029; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements., 1905; MS102.002.010.DO.00030; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements., 1905; MS102.002.010.DO.00031; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements., 1905; MS102.002.010.DO.00032; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements., 1905; MS102.002.010.DO.00033; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements., 1905; MS102.002.010.DO.00034; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements., 1905; MS102.002.010.DO.00035; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements., 1905; MS102.002.010.DO.00036; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Advertisements., 1905; MS102.002.010.DO.00037; Sampson & Murdock Co.
    - Banks., 1905; MS102.002.010.DO.00038; Sampson & Murdock Co.
      Page image of Banks from the 1905 Boston city directory. Institute of Museum and Library Services
    - Banks., 1905; MS102.002.010.DO.00039; Sampson & Murdock Co.